Guide to the Steffi Domike Papers, 1946-2009 AIS.1997.20
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Oversize Material, 1912-2000; XIV.
  - Work In Progress: A Festival of Steel, Sweat and American Cinema, poster, 2000 (Map-case 16, Drawer 13, Folder 4)
  - Homestead Strike Centennial Poster, 1992 (Map-case 16, Drawer 14, Folder 1)
  - Maxo Vanka's Millvale Murals Poster, circa 1981 (Map-case 16, Drawer 14, Folder 2)
  - Aerial photograph of the Monongahela River Valley, from the junction with the Youghiogheny River to the Point (Map-case 16, Drawer 14, Folder 3)
- The River Ran Red Image Binders, XV.
  This series contains images used for the research and production of the film The River Ran Red. Domike originally organized the images in four binders and various categories. Each of Domike's original categories corresponds with a folder within the series.
  - Image Binder Content Sheet Files 1-8 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Portraits Section (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Homestead Overview Section (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Workers in Mill Section (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Community(Lifestyle and Misc. Portraits) Section (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Britian, Scotland Section (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Labor History Section (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Battle Section (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Surrender Section (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Image Binder Content Sheet Files 9-16 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Occupational/Militia Section (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Aftermath Section (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Pittsburgh Section (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Other Mill Shots Section (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Coking (Towns and Industry) Section (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Headlines Section (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Image Binder Content Sheet Files 17-24 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous (Bridges) Section (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Pinkertons Section (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - U.S. Capitol and Misc. Locations Section (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Political Cartoons/Politics Section (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Telegrams and Letters Section (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Anarchism Section (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Trains, Oil Industry Section (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Homestead Millshots Section (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Edgar Thompson/Braddock Section (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Mills: Duquesne; N&L Tube Words, Carnegie Steel, Etna, J&L/ADs Section (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Image Binder Content Sheet Files 28-31 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Bridge Section (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - River: Dam and Boats Barges Section (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Gilded Age Section (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - Vanka Murals, St. Nicholas Section (Box 78, Folder 31)